PAYAL REWARI

About me

Highly skilled and motivated French language expert in Business consulting with software implementation (SAP Concur) experience. Worked in different organizations as an Underwriter Assistant in Insurance (RSA) and responsible customer support in Amazon. Working as a translator from French to English & vice-versa.

contact



+91 - 8826961930



Payalrewari86@gmail.com



Delhi. India



https://www.linkedin.com/in/payalrewari-825393160

EDUCATION

Delhi University

B.A. (Economics, Consumer Affairs, Political Science)

B.M.S.K.V, Delhi (Commerce) 12th

10th from Vidya Vihar School, (CBSE) Delhi

Alliance Française de Delhi

(French B2) **Langma School of languages** (French B2)

Diplôme d'études en langue française (DELF A2 & B1)

Bronze award for good performance (Genpact) **Spot Award (EY)**

- **Empathetic And Communicative Abilities**
- Microsoft Word, Excel & Outlook
- Power BI
- **PowerPoint**
- **SAP Concur Implementation**
- Agile Methodology
 - CAT tools Smartcat, memoQ

Professional Experience

May 2021 - Present

SENIOR BUSINESS CONSULTANT, ERNST & YOUNG (EY) (GURGAON)

- Experienced in Project Management Office (PMO) roles.
- Good knowledge of Agile methodologies.
- 2 years of experience working with different levels of software deployment testing
- Manges multiple ends-to-end implementations for clients simultaneously, acting in the role of SAP Concur Functional/Implementation consultant, encompassing the following responsibilities.
- Gather, define and document different business requirements using Microsoft Excel from EMEA countries.
- Provide User Acceptance Testing (UAT), Base Test Plans, Detailed Test Plans for UAT and step-by-step test scripts for UAT using ALM Tool.
- Maintained smooth execution of software deployment by giving end-to-end process training to the testers from EMEA.
- Concur Travel & Expense Implementation and end-to-end integration along with good experience in Cognos reporting tools and report builds.
- After go-live, provide configuration related hypercare support in EY Paris office.
- Worked on as an PMO on various projects were:
 - Tracking & managing budgets, creating schedules, progress check and deliverables.
 - Budget vs Actuals analysis, Pricing Plan, doing Estimate to Company (ETC) & Invoicing.

UNDERWRITER ASSISTANT, GENPACT (NOIDA)

- Worked for Royal Sun Alliance (Quebec) Insurance group as an underwriter assistant, responsible for providing Commercial Insurance in Auto & Property in Quebec region.
- Created SOP's and gave process trainings to the onshore's in French.
- Responsible for insurance submission clearance, endorsement & renewal processing.
- Liaise with insurer partners to retrieve and then in coordination with the Broker review policy documentation (quotes, binders, policies) to ensure coverage requirements have been met, completing the policy checklists.
- Handled varied volumes of workloads and to reach targets and deadlines on a timely basis.
- Responsible for internal auditing of the cases to ensure the accuracy.

June 2018 - Feb 2019

CUSTOMER CARE EXECUTIVE (AMAZON.FR), CONCENTRIX (GURGAON)

- Solved customer issues related to delivery of products via calls/emails in French & English.
- Dedicated to bettering the customer experience with Amazon France with reliable product education, timely assistance and respectful conflict management services.
- Provided replacements, reimbursement or cancellation of a product/ Amazon services if required.
- Created organizational success and advancing brand reputation through serving customers in a truly memorable way.

Jan 2018 – Present

Freelance Translator (French ↔ English

- Highly experienced in translating the documents (Medical, Legal, literature) from English to French and vice versa.
- Worked with "The Hustler Collective" & "Gianey & Daughters Financial Services etc.
- Familiar with using the CAT tools like Smartcat, memoQ & Trados.
- Prioritize the delivery of the tasks with high accuracy and within the given timeline